Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford Collection 0013.123.001
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
Newsletters 2007
Newsletters 2008-2009
Newsletters 2010-
Box 24: Outreach – Publications/Connecticut Jewish History, Volume I
Outreach/Lotstein, Marsha/Presentations to other organizations
Outreach/Miscellaneous
Outreach/Miscellaneous
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/Connecticut History Journals/Editors
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/Volume 1 and 2/Marketing
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/Volume 1/Correspondence/Kahn, Lothar
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/Volume 1/Endowment Grant, 1989
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/Volume 1/Final copy
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/volume 1/Journal Committee Minutes, 1988-1990
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/Volume 1/Miscellaneous Materials from Lothar Kahn
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/volume 1/original submissions
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/Volume 1/Printing and Publishing Information
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/Volume 1/Research Notes/Kopplemann
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/Volume 1/Research Notes/Kahn, Lothar
Box 25: Publications/Connecticut Jewish History, v. 2 and 3
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/Volume 2/fundraiser
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/Volume 2/General
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/Volume 2/Manuscript/Draft
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/Volume 2/Marketing
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/Volume 2/Mechanicals Cover
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/Volume 2/100 years: Synagogue architectural survey
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/Volume 3/Committee
Publications/Connecticut Jewish History/Volume 3/Patrons and Sponsors
Publications/Making a Life: Building a Community, see JHSGH/Special Projects and University of Hartford and Morris and Emma Cohen Collections
Box 26/Can't find this box
Publicity/Bookmarks
Publicity/Brochures,
Publicity/Brochures,
Publicity/Brochures, 1971-1972
Publicity/Brochures, 1972-1973
Publicity/Brochures, 1973-1974
Publicity/Brochures, 1974-1975
Publicity/Brochures, 1975-1976
Publicity/Brochures, 1976-1977
Publicity/Brochures, 1977-1978
Publicity/Brochures, 1978-1979
Publicity/Brochures, 1979-1980
Publicity/Brochures, 1980-1981
Publicity/Brochures, 1981-1982
Publicity/Brochures, 1983-1984
Publicity/Brochures, late 1980s and early 1990s
Publicity/Logo
Publicity/OVERSIZE, in oversize box on shelf
Box 27: Trips and Tours
Trips and Tours/1975 June 18/Brandeis University
Trips and Tours/1976 May 10/New York City
Trips and Tours/1977 May 4/New York City
Trips and Tours/1978 May 1/Hartford
Trips and Tours/1979 May 15/New York City
Trips and Tours/1979 Nov. 4/Old State House and Wadsworth Atheneum
Trips and Tours/1980 April 24/New York City
Trips and Tours/1980 Nov. 20/Hartford Architecture
Trips and Tours/1981 April 1/Boston MA
Trips and Tours/1981 Aug. 10/Charter Oak Temple
Trips and Tours/1982 May 5/New York City
Trips and Tours/1987 April 30/New York City
Trips and Tours/1993 Aug. 1-3/Washington DC
Trips and Tours/1994 June 12-14/Washington DC
Trips and Tours/1996 Aug 18-20/Washington DC
Trips and Tours/Games
Box 28: Special Projects/Miscellaneous
"Special Projects" include ventures that comprised several facets such as an exhibit, publication, and meeting program, or which didn't fall into any of these three categories.
Some of the folders in Box 28 are missing. They may have been refilled in a different place
Special Projects/1954/Tercentenary
Special Projects/1970s-present/Oral History
Special Projects/1978/Roots
Special Projects/1982/Jewish War Veterans
Special Projects/1982/Emanuel Synagogue
Special Projects/1983/Jewish Day
Special Projects/1989/Grocery Stores
Special Projects/1996/Archives
Special Projects/1998/Tribute to Lewis Fox at Fox Middle School, with Eve Soumerai
Special Projects/2002/Greater Hartford Jewish Community History Project, funded by Zachs Family Foundation
Special Projects/2002/Memoirs/Trips to Israel
Special Projects/2002/Memoir Workshop
Special Projects/1999-2002/Memoir workshop/Leader: Len Cohen
Special Projects/2006/North End/Oral History
Box 29: Special Projects/1995/Soviet Jewish World War II Exhibit/Jewish War Veterans
This project consisted of an exhibit and an oral history program and led to the Witness to War project carried out during the 2000s. Some tapes are related to the Witness to War project.
Nov. 2000 Betty Hoffman/ JFS citizenship class at Beth Israel
Newest Americans, Betty Hoffman
Soviet Jewish Experience Esfir Kraimore
Box 30: Special Projects/2009/Hartford North End Project
This project consisted of a book that was the compilation of more that 150 memories from people growing up in Hartford's North End (predominately Jewish members of community but not exclusively)
Special Projects/2009/Hartford North End Book/Book Launch
Special Projects/2009/Hartford North End Book/Book: Remembering the Old Neighboorhood
Special Projects/2009/Hartford North End Book/Interview Information
Special Projects/2009/Hartford North End Book/Jewish Ledger
Special Projects/2009/Hartford North End Book/North End Narrators/DVD
Special Projects/2009/Hartford North End Book/PowerPoint shown at Book Opening/Photographs
Special Projects/2009/Hartford North End Book/Publicity
Special Projects/2009/Hartford North End Book/Request for Information/Stories
Special Projects/2009/Hartford North End /Donated Photos/October 2009
Special Projects/2009/Hartford North End /Donated Photos/2010
Special Projects/Hartford North End/Leadership Greater Hartford North End program
Box 31: Special Projects/2012/Hartford North End Project II
Special Projects/Hartford North End/Book II/Donated Images/ 2010
Special Projects/Hartford North End/Book II/Elston, Rosalyn Millstein
Special Projects/Hartford North End/Book II/Images 2010-2012
Witness to War
Due to the large number of Witness to War materials, these boxes are numbered separately from the rest of the JHSGH collection.
Two boxes containing information on publicity and exhibits.
Witness to War: The Soviet Jewish Experience 1941-1945 was a major traveling exhibit conceived of and created by the JHSGH. The project involved the interviewing and videotaping of numerous Russian-Americans of the World War II generation. The project resulted in two end products: the traveling exhibit and a volume of Connecticut Jewish History dedicated to the topic. This collection contains the original videotapes, transcripts in both Russian and English, and administrative files related to the project.
Witness to War was coordinated by JHSGH Director Marsh Lotstein and Dr. Betty Hoffman, historian. The exhibit was designed by Harrison (Whitey) Jenkins. Jeffrey Mills designed the brochure and Diana McCain provided publicity services.
Special Projects/Witness to War, Box 1: Witness Transcripts
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Witness List
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Aronov, Marc
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Domnich, Genya
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Frenkel, Mariya
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Freydzoh, Gdal
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Gekhman, Aron
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Ginsburg, Boris
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Grabarnik, Lazar
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Gupper, Naum
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Izikson, Abram
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Kaganovich, Israel
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Kaplan, Vladimir
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Khaimova, Esfir
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Korobochko, Bina
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Krant, Lena
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Livshits, Sarra
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Medovy, Yakov
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Militskiy, Michael
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Murakovskiy, Israel Mura
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Peskin, Vladimir
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Polyakov, Boris
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Prokopets, Ides
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Reker, Michael
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Rozovsky, Yefim
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Sandal, Maryam
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Simkhovich, Izya
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Toger, Yakov
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Treyster, Milya
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Tseytlin, Zhemya
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Yacob, Olga
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/Zeygerman, Yosif
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/unidentified
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/unidentified
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/unidentified
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/unidentified
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/Russian/unidentified
Special Projects/Witness to War/Witnesses/Kogan, Hyman (Chaim)/Autobiography dictated to volunteers
Box 1a Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English Note: these files also contain release forms
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Aronov, Mark
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Aronov, Nina
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Besnosov, Mikhail
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Blekhman, Lyusya
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Bratslavsky, Anna
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Domnich, Genya
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Frenkel, Mariya
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Freydzon, Gdal
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Gelman, Seman
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Grabarnik, Lazar
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Greydinger, Boris
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Gupper, Naum
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Izikson, Abram
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Kaganovich, Israel
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Kaplan, Vladimir
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Khaimova, Esafir
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Kogan, Hyman
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Korobochko, Bina
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Krant, Lena
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Leykikh, Frima
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Livshits, Sarra
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Lundina, Roza
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Medovoy, Yakov
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Metlitsky, Michael
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Murakhovskiy, Israel
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Pekar, Michael
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Peskin, Vladimir
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Polyakov, Boris
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Prokopets, Lida (Ides)
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Rozovsky, Yefim
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Rytman, Dora
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Rytman, Julius
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Sandal, Maryam
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Simkhovich, Izya
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Toger, Ykov
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Treyster, Milya
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Tseytlin, Zhenya
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Virkerman, Anna
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Yacub, Olga
Special Projects/Witness to War/Transcripts/English/Zeygerman, Iosif
Special Projects/Witness to War/Administrative
Special Projects/Witness to War/Brochures and Flyers
Special Projects/Witness to War/Exhibition/Exhibition Labels
Special Projects/Witness to War/Exhibition/Materials
Special Projects/Witness to War/Exhibition/Materials (2)
Special Projects/Witness to War/Exhibition/Script
Special Projects/Witness to War/Exhibition/Script (2)
Special Projects/Witness to War/Exhibition/Venues
Special Projects/Witness to War/Finances
Special Projects/Witness to War/Grants
Special Projects/Witness to War/Grants (2)
Special Projects/Witness to War/Media
Special Projects/Witness to War/News Clippings
Special Projects/Witness to War/Opening Exhibit (JCC)
Special Projects/Witness to War/Photographs
Special Projects/Witness to War/Release Forms
Special Projects/Witnesses/Kogan, Hyman (Chaim) Autobiography
Special Projects/Witness to War, Box 2: Miscellaneous
Special Projects/Witness to War, Box 3: Miscellaneous
One box of miscellaneous materials.
Special Projects/Witness to War, Boxes 4 to 6: Videotapes Special Projects/1998/Witness to War/ Videotapes/Three large record center boxes of videotapes, now (July 2005) stored in archives room (where Farming and Immigration Collections are stored) under glass shelves.
Special Projects/Witness to War, Boxes 7: Miscellaneous
Scrapbooks
2 boxes of scrapbooks Publicity, exhibits and other scrapbooks
Zoosman, Michael/History of Conservative Movement
One box of manuscript material in Aisle 7A
Kafer, Estelle, Executive Director of Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
- Series I: Administration, A-Correspondence, 1980s
  - Administration/Accessions and Loans, notebook, 1970s
  - Administration/Acquisitions, 1970s
  - Administration/Correspondence/1975
  - Administration/Correspondence/1976
  - Administration/Correspondence/1977
  - Administration/Correspondence/1978
  - Administration/Correspondence/1979
  - Administration/Correspondence/1980
  - Administration/Correspondence/1981
  - Administration/Correspondence/1982
  - Administration/Correspondence/1983
  - Administration/Correspondence/1984
  - Administration/Correspondence/1985
  - Administration/Correspondence/1986
  - Administration/Correspondence/1987
  - Administration/Correspondence/1988
  - Administration/Correspondence/1989
- Series II: Administration/Correspondence, 1990s-2000s
  - Administration/Correspondence/1990
  - Administration/Correspondence/1991
  - Administration/Correspondence/1992
  - Administration/Correspondence/1993
  - Administration/Correspondence/1994
  - Administration/Correspondence/1995
  - Administration/Correspondence/1996
  - Administration/Correspondence/1997
  - Administration/Correspondence/1998
  - Administration/Correspondence/1999
  - Administration/Correspondence/2000
  - Administration/Correspondence/2001
  - Administration/Correspondence/2002
  - Administration/Correspondence/Archives/Margaret Mair/2000s, undated
  - Administration/Correspondence/Genealogy Inquiries and Responses, 1970s-2000s, undated
- Series III: Administration/Equipment: Board of Directors/Meeting Notices
  - Administration/Eqipment//Ikon-105 Capital copier, 2000s, undated
  - Administration/Equipment/A-copy Cannon Copier, 1990s, undated
  - Administration/Librarian's reports, 1976-1983
  - Administration/Museum Assessment/MAP, Marsha Lotstein has as of 6/29/05, undated
  - Administration/Museum Assessment/MAP I/administrative material, 1997, undated
  - Administration/Mission Statement, c. 1990s
  - Administration/Museum Assessment, 1997
  - Administration/Staff, undated
  - Administration/Staff/Executive Directors/Lotstein, Marsha 1982-2004
  - Administration/Staff/Executive Directors/Kafer, Estelle, 2004-
  - Administration/Staff/Rudolph, Shayna/Aliyah, 2007
  - Administration/Staff/Job descriptions, undated
  - Awards and proclamations, undated
  - Board of Directors/By-laws, undated
  - Board of Directors/Executive Committee, undated
  - Board of Directors/Incorporation Papers, undated
  - Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/1971-1980/Emma Cohen
  - Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/1980-1982/M.Delott Garber
  - Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/1982-1987/Morris Handler
  - Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/1987-1992/Joseph Hurwitz
  - Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/1992-1994/Jerry Wagner
  - Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/1994-1996/Leon Chameides
  - Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/1996-1998/Seymour Saltzman
  - Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/1998-2001/David Klau
  - Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/2001-2002/Lea Rubenstein
  - Board of Directors/Meeting Notices/2004-/Art Nassau
- Series IV: Board of Directors/Meetings/2012
  - Board of Directors/Minutes/M. Delott Garber, undated
  - Board of Directors/Meetings/President Emma Cohen's notes, 1971-1980, undated
  - Board of Directors/Members/1971-1981, undated
  - Board of Directors/Members/1979-1980, undated
  - Board of Directors/Members/1982-1992, undated
  - Board of Directors/Members/1993-2003, undated
  - Board of Directors/Members/1996-1997, undated
  - Board of Directors/Members/2005-2006, undated
  - Board of Directors/Members/Presidents/, undated
  - Board of Directors/Members/Presidents/Cohen, Emma/Correspondence, 1970s, undated
  - Board of Directors/Members/Presidents/Cohen, Emma/Notebook, 1970s, undated
  - Board of Directors/Minute Book, earliest minutes, 1970s, undated
  - Board of Directors/Minutes/1970s, undated
  - Board of Directors/Minutes/1982/M. Delott Garber, undated
- Series V: Board of Directors/Minutes/Morris Handler-Z
  - Board of Directors/Minutes/1982-1987/Morris Handler
  - Board of Directors/Minutes/1987-1992/Joseph Hurwitz
  - Board of Directors/Minutes/1992-1994/Jerry Wagner
  - Board of Directors/Minutes/1994-1996/Leon Chameides
  - Board of Directors/Minutes/1996-1998/Seymour Saltzman
  - Board of Directors/Minutes/1998-2000/David Klau
  - Board of Directors/Minutes/2001-2002/Lea Rubenstein
  - Board of Directors/Minutes/2003-/Arthur Nassau, undated
  - Board of Directors/Miscellaneous/1990s-2000s, 1990-2000
  - Board of Directors/Nominating Committee/Notes by President Emma Cohen 1970s, undated
  - Board of Directors/Program Committee, 1970s, undated
  - Board of Directors/Program Committee, 1980s, undated
  - Board of Directors/Program Committee, 1990s, undated
- Series VI: Conferences
  - Conferences/1991/American Jewish Historical Society Conference in Hartford/One box of materials, undated
- Series VII: Exhibits, 1960s-1970s
  - Exhibit files are filed chronologically by date of installation. Exhibit panels of many of the larger exhibits are currently (August 2006) filed in large flat boxes on the exhibit shelves. See also scrapbooks and oversize., undated
  - Exhibits/1968/Lower East Side and Hartford Jews
  - Exhibits/1975/Emanuel Synagogue/American Jewish Experience
  - Exhibits/1975/Long Time Residents of the Hartford Area
  - Exhibits/1976/Exhibits/Bicentennial
  - Exhibits/1976/Ruth Wyllys Chapter, DAR/Photographs of Early Hartford Scenes
  - Exhibits/1976/Scott-Fanton Museum, Danbury/Jewish Life in Connecticut since 1976
  - Exhibits/1977/Emanuel Synagogue/Discovery: Our Fathers and Grandfathers
  - Exhibits/1977/Lewis Fox
  - Exhibits/1977/Our Community At Work
  - Exhibits/1977/South Windsor Library/Old Hartford and Jewish War Veterans
  - Exhibits/1978/Sixty Years of Zionism
  - Exhibits/1978/Sixty Years of Zionism/Book, to be published, 2 folders
- Series VIII: Exhibits 1980s-2000s: Facilities
  - Exhibits/1980/Contribution of Hartford Jewry to the City's Arts
  - Exhibits/1981/Avon Public Library/Jewish History in the Hartford Area
  - Exhibits/1981/Windsor Public Library/Fox Family
  - Exhibits/1981/Wood Memorial Library/Jewish Ceremonial Objects
  - Exhibits/1982/Emanuel Synagogue/Rabbi Israel Goldfarb
  - Exhibits/1983/Jewish Family Expo
  - Exhibits/1985/A Shayna Maidel
  - Exhibits/1985/Hartford's Jewish Community: Yesterday and Today
  - Exhibits/1986/West Hartford Public Library/Yiddish documents, Newspapers, and Ephemera
  - Exhibits/1987/Agudas Achim/100th Anniversary. See also one oversize box of exhibit materials in Aisle 9
  - Exhibits/1988/Annie Fisher: A Remembrance 1883-1968
  - Exhibits/1995/Holocaust room
  - Exhibits/1996/The Way We Were
  - Exhibits/1998/Israel at 50
  - Exhibits/1999/Portraits of New Americans
  - Exhibits/1999/The Passover Haggadah: a Jewish Cultural Phenomenon
  - Exhibits/2004/Charter Oak Temple/ photographs
  - Exhibits/2000s/Synagogues, 3 oversize boxes and one pile of panels not in boxes, undated
  - Exhibits/2007/Hartford Remembers Sophie Tucker, see also Families and Individuals/Tucker, Sophie
  - Exhibits/2008/"Documenting Life and Destruction: Emanuel Ringelbum and the Oneg Shabbes Archive"
  - Exhibits/2008/"The Hartford-Israel Connection: A Century of Commitment"
  - Exhibits/2008/Israel at 60
  - Exhibits/2010/A Reason to Remember
  - Facilities/Community Services Building, 2000s, undated
  - Facilities/Jewish Community Center, undated
  - Facilities/Jewish Community Center/Open House, 1991
- Series XV: Financial/Check Stubs/2012
  - Financial/Check Stubs/1011-1160, 2/15/96-5/15/97, 1996-1997
  - Financial/Check Stubs/1461-1535, 7/21/99-12/27/99, 1999-1999
  - Financial/Check Stubs/1536-1601, 12/30/99-5/26/00, 1999-2000
  - Financial/Check Stubs/1611-1685, undated
  - Financial/Check Stubs/1651-1800, 6/3/86-4/25/88, 1986-1988
  - Financial/Check Stubs/1686-1760, 10/10/00-2/28/01, 2000-2001
  - Financial/Check Stubs/1761-1835, 2/25/01-7/16/01, 2001-2001
  - Financial/Check Stubs/1801-1950, 5/1/88-10/1/89, 1988-1989
  - Financial/Check Stubs/1911-1985, 7/12/01-11/28/01, 2001-2001
  - Financial/Check Stubs/1951-2100, 10/15/89-2/21/91, 1989-1991
  - Financial/Check Stubs/2101-2250, 2/28/91-5/30/92, 1991-1992
  - Financial/Check Stubs/2251-2400, 6/11/92-10/15/93, 1992-1993
  - Financial/Check Stubs/2401-2550, 10/18/93-12/30/94, 1993-1994
  - Financial/Check Stubs/2551-2680, 12/30/94-1/18/96, 1994-1996
- Series XVI, XVII: Financial/Deposit Slips, budget, matching grants, taxes Box 17, last few folders: Fundraising.
  - Financial/Deposit Slips, FY 1996
  - Financial/Deposit Slips, FY 1997
  - Financial/Deposit Slips, FY 1998
  - Financial/Deposit/Membership, 1988-1996
  - Financial/First Bank of West Hartford/CD, 1994-1995
  - Financial/First Bank of West Hartford/CD, 1996
  - Financial/Funding/Jewish Federation, undated
  - Financial/Matching Allocations, 1990-1991; 1991-1992, 1990-1992
  - Financial/Matching Allocations, 1992-1993
  - Financial/Matching Allocations, 1993-1994
  - Financial/Matching Allocations, 1994-1996
  - Financial/Matching Allocations, 1996-1997
  - Financial/Matching Allocations, 1997-1998
  - Financial/Matching Allocations, 1998-1999
  - Financial/Budget, 1980s, 1980-1989
  - Financial/Budget, 1990-1992
  - Financial/Budget, 1992-1993
  - Financial/Budget, 1994
  - Financial/Budget, 1995
  - Financial/Budget, 1996-1996
  - Financial/Budget, 1998
  - Financial/Budget, 1999
  - Financial/Budget, 1990-, undated
  - Financial/Deposit Record, 1996
  - Financial/Deposit Record, 1997
  - Financial/Tax Records, 1991-1993
  - Financial/Tax Records, 1994-1996
  - Financial/Tax Returns, 1991-1993
  - Financial/Tax Returns, 1994-1996
  - Financial/Tax Returns, 1995-, undated
  - Fundraising/Endowment Funds, 1990s-2000s, 1990-2000
  - Fundraising/Grants/Endowment, 1985
  - Fundraising/Used Book Sale, 1992
  - Grants/Endowment Foundation Transition Funds Request, Jewish Community Foundation, 2004, undated
- Series XVIII: Hall of Fame, 1980s
  - Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/1982
  - Hall of Fame for Greater Hartford Jewish Athletes/1983/Newspaper clippings